<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-03-10T03:11:06-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Wolf Blog</title><subtitle>Blog about wolves</subtitle><author><name>Alexander</name></author><entry><title type="html">Wolves in Gaming</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/09/wolves-in-gaming.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wolves in Gaming" /><published>2020-03-09T07:45:13-07:00</published><updated>2020-03-09T07:45:13-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/09/wolves-in-gaming</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/09/wolves-in-gaming.html">&lt;p&gt;Wolves are very common in gaming. Most of the time you may see them as wild enemies in RPGs, but there are some stand out others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lets look through some of them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/gaming/wolf-link.png&quot; alt=&quot;Wolf Link and Midna&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;&quot;In our world, we've long believed that the Hero would appear as a divine beast.&quot; — Midna&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Wolf Link - The Legend of Zelda&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This half counts but counts all the same. Wolf link is a form that the hero Link takes when exposed to the twilight in &lt;i&gt;The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This quickly becomes hindrance as much as it becomes a valuble tool for Link since he has hightened senses and a more mobile frame for the exchange of no longer being able to use any of his other items.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This feature in &lt;i&gt;Twilight Princess&lt;/i&gt; was always controversial since segments you had to play as wolf link were often slow and tedious. Despite that, he remains a popular character in the Zelda series, getting an Amiibo figure and being added as an extra feature in &lt;i&gt;The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/gaming/sif.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Great Grey Wolf Sif&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;The Great Grey Wolf Sif&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Sif - Dark Souls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sif is a boss in &lt;i&gt;Dark Souls&lt;/i&gt;, and probably the saddest one at that. Sif gaurds the grave of Artorias the Abysswalker who Sif was partner to. After he was swallowed by the abyss Sif took to gaurd his grave so that it would not happen to anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite technically being an enemy to Sif, you need Artorias' ring to continue and so Sif defends the grave. As Sif nears death their movements are slowed with a limp until you finally finish the fight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A bittersweet ending to what truely is, a good boy, or girl, it is never defined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/gaming/lycanroc.png&quot; alt=&quot;Lycanroc&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Midday Form Lycanroc&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Lycanroc - Pokemon&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For as long as the Pokemon series has ran I was always suprised and disapointed a wolf pokemon was never around. There were really close ones but none based directly off of a wolf. Until Gen 7 gave us Lycanroc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lycanroc is semi special in that it has a few different forms depending on when and what version it evolves on. It has 3 forms: Midday, Midnight, and Dusk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pokemon decided to even show how sorry they were for never having any other wolf pokemon so they made the legendaries for Gen 8 two wolves!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/gaming/Zacian.png&quot; alt=&quot;Lycanroc&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Zacian&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/gaming/Zamazenta.png&quot; alt=&quot;Lycanroc&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Zamazeta&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nice right? Zacian even has been compared to Sif due to their use of a longsword held between their mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/gaming/ammy.png&quot; alt=&quot;Okami Amaturasu&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;&quot;Ah...Amaterasu. Origin of all that is good and mother to us all.&quot; -Sakuya&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Amaterasu - Okami&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saving the best for last, and my personal favorite, is non-other than Amaterasu from &lt;i&gt;Okami&lt;/i&gt;. Often called &quot;Ammy&quot; by her companion Issun, she is the incarnation of the goddess Amaterasu in wolf form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a god you have powers to affect the world around you. This power manifests as a brush and allows Ammy to solve problems and fight with a versitile set of brush strokes she can use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Okami&lt;/i&gt; came out at a very close time to &lt;i&gt;The Legend of Zelda: Twilight Princess&lt;/i&gt; and was not only compared to it with it's wolf protaginists but also that it's gameplay is inpired a lot by the Zelda series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite pieces of trivia for this game comes in its title, it's a pun! &quot;Okami&quot; is the word for wolf in japanese, but how it is written out there reads more like &quot;O-Kami&quot; which better translates to &quot;Great God&quot; Pretty great right?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Alexander</name></author><summary type="html">Wolves are very common in gaming. Most of the time you may see them as wild enemies in RPGs, but there are some stand out others. Lets look through some of them!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">I made a blog about wolves so you don’t have to!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/01/wolves.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I made a blog about wolves so you don't have to!" /><published>2020-03-01T06:45:13-08:00</published><updated>2020-03-01T06:45:13-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/03/01/wolves</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/03/01/wolves.html">&lt;p&gt;This is something that I have always wanted to do!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I may succeed or fail at it. We will have to see&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;On the subject of Wolves&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The focus of this blog is on of course, wolves! What is there to talk about? A lot more than you may think. Sure there may be slow times when there is not much to say, but there is always something interesting to talk about&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Here's to a great start!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/img/posts/wolf1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Demo Image&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Awoo&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy to have you along for the ride!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Alexander</name></author><summary type="html">This is something that I have always wanted to do! I may succeed or fail at it. We will have to see</summary></entry></feed>